Team into wild animals Released: www.HoundDawgs.org
I'll be there.
Impasse?
Thank you. Mad magazine.
A group calling? I am in the chamber 2.
Nova ... the cave is safe.
Are you okay? What do you need?
Shepardin order.
Shepard! I'm not the Ravenwood.
Both me and NATO. we are grateful that the US has decided to lähettää- -
- Best haisotilaansa this crisis.
When the President. the United Nations and Europe to help your father asks. can not deny.
I'll be up to the Parliament at the NATO crisis.
And he? Gil. If you say something.
Other children are cleaning up the last traces of the attack at home.
Paratus.- always do. Dad? Yes. my son.
Mr. Shepard. is busy to call you.
Hello? Nova. where are you? We are going to a meeting of NATO strategy.
Where is that?
Where is Nova? -Here.
After riding the Eiffel Tower did not cross the Atlantic in Nova?
Yes. I know him well.
Be careful. It's really deep.
Do not worry. You done this before -Have?
I have done it all before. What's it say?
Mission accomplished. If you got in your mouth. cruise.
I would say that ruined the task. Where did you learn to ride?
Hey. Finn. Has been yearning for? -Hey. Nova.
I saw my family sharks motor has been saved. Now I'm afraid of sharks.
A little rebellious. Yes. I appreciate the joint moments.
No need to keep in mind the smell. but not in the family.
Why do we have to stop reading? -Näin to protect the family.
Here. Llewelyn will take care of you.
Ah. Shepard. Too bad -Not.
You can conveniently display the latest UK has a gun.
You shark. lontoolaiset- announcement should come - if
- elegant and powerful weapons.
ফিউরিয়াস. -panka পুতুল আকৃতি.
Wait a minute.
Well. Llewelyn.- helmet head.
So. you have need of them.
The best thing to go low.
Two clicks with the pen. and ...
Not bad. huh?
Apparently you have wings. but you get to fly for real.
That's it. This is a suitable size.
The fiber optic bubble results. It stacks up to the storm.
The order contains a transmitter to know where it is.
Earth mother. I hear.
What's going on here? This stone is cut.
This was before the storm. Every corner of the planet.
They are not only fighting against the harmful nadoja. but won.
How? -That's Dukuwagan armor.
মিনকা? -Haijumalan.
ijumalan course.
Druids hainadoja protection against. and has been used as a map mukaan- -
- It is hidden in a cave. So to get it -Tulit.
No. we came to pick it up.
We have always worked together. I could not give up now.
You also seem to have missed me.
How do you know that it's not just the fiction haijumalajuttu?
It is history. Sisarkuntani the sand. Jerusalem is finding ...
Sister municipality? I met a few hainado sister.
Say it is not a cult band.
Sharks ...
Why do you always sharks?
Hip!
There it is.
Wait
See. My taste -Not.
But this I can take.
wait. Here you can have traps.
Herrajumala ...
See.
Do not! We need a counterweight.
Megalodon? I'm out of my collection.
Stonehenge explode.
Visually vibrant!
They are watching us!
I said.
I do not need your help. Bring your own harness.
আপনি SSH বললে? -Kiipeä.
Go to!
No. Finn!
We got it. But we launched haimaailmansodan.
Go from here.
Andromeda's! Let's go to
Start helicopter!
What happens then? Hai -sama every day.
Dana. where are you? -About 10 kilometers away from London.
Hainado made clear Stonehenge. -Pyörremyrsky coming here.
Go to the RAF helicopter landing zone.
Your family is waiting for you. You -See.
Father. can you hear me? -bad signal.
Jeff Rossen London. which is reported to haitsunami.
She has organized a fleet outside the city.
Welcome back. -We have the latest news.
Weather warnings for London. a red alarm condition.
London hainado approaching the -10 level.
London was attacked. What should I? We are in a traffic jam.
London the whole. they are currently empty.
All are advised to watch out for storms.
You should not tease. fight back. ironed. and the sharks will not eat.
It's ready? -Varmasti. This will be fun.
We give up the bridge. It is not safe.
Mother obeyed. He knows.
Now. get out quickly and under your feet!
Is everything okay? I'm not sure.
Father!
Do not! The safety of my son -Export.
Hold on. we're going down!
Father. yes it was cool!
Well done. I have no one to do it.
Fine lakki.- sharks so that they think I am one of them.
I Skyfall. Coming soon.
London Bridge collapses! -It will not last. Let's get started!
Will be a car! Okay. come quickly. '
Sir. you need to avoid the risk of not being able to settle down.
I was pahemmissakin space. Now. hunters can not catch it.
Nova has organized a ride. -from?
If you need a ride?
Go to the Palace. There are safe. But. sir. for your feet!
Contact hainadotorjunta trigger. -Sir. I love you.
Are you kidding?
It's about time. I've been waiting for this for a long time.
Gil. save the mother. Right outside hazel grouse. Dad.
Finn. how it works?
My God. I just killed Brett Michaelsin!
All very good. On -Hold!
Be careful. They are on the road.
Finn. difficulties.
I was annoyed by them. No wonder.
wait.
The holiday tastes. But the kind of beach.
It does not get better than this work.
wait!
Come on.
The storm is approaching. From here to fix the bone.
The queen eats a farmer.
You can catch me! Tom Daley jump from the bridge.
This has been seen before. -It must be. Soon. all will die.
It is approaching Big Ben. What I can not take care of it.
Let's go.
Export Gil security. I am coming. Come on. Gil.
We want to help parents. Gil. Nova save!
From Tule. -Okei Nova.
Get down!
Unfortunately Hainado is approaching Buckingham Palace.
The Queen has been known to do get trapped there.
Sharks have blocked all the entrances.
If hainado palace strikes. losses will be valtavat- -
- not only in the UK but around the world.
Can you help please?
Teidänhän queen. must be protected is not true? It is now in place.
Now. you either fight or die. What is being done?
Let's fight!
Nova. you will save!
Nova. come on! Me your hand -Give.
Nova! On -Hold!
Gil!
God forbid that the queen.
What? Gil.
Where is he? Hold him -Yritin.
It happened so fast. I held on with all my strength.
The storm was very violent. Than ever rougher.
It makes my arms wrenched. -Päästitkö day he has to go?
I have done my duty. -You should not have let him.
Why do you always defend him? -Anteeksi that I am only human.
Finn. he's gone back to him ... -Saamme.
Whatever it was immediately.
Oh. my God! Then. it is Gil. He -Elääkö?
Radar tracked live. Netherlands 850 km per hour. he flies to.
He lived! Holland? This is the helmet.
It protects him. even a storm. even hainadossakin.
Go get him. -How?
NATO! I am the source of any meeting.
The world's leading scientists are meeting in London.
If you want your son back. they only hope.
I should not have to go to the cave. It all started with that.
We'll find him. I promise that I will not disappoint.
Welcome back. England has been terrible in the morning.
Fortunately. the storm has subsided.
We have heard that millionaires and researcher Gerald Michael Angel- -
- future hainadoja represents a new aircraft weapons.
On XP. 3000 hindenabarga Sen nimi.
Airship? It's the -Lykkyä.
They are reliable friends. It quickly -Tehdään.
What the Chinese do with the waste?
Self fantastic mobile phones? I do not think so. "Order!"
China has kindly tarjoutunut- -
- Subscribe to receive the latest hainadon nuclear waste.
The storm caused a nuclear disaster.
ট্রাই Wobbegon. -New ...
I'm sorry. I'm labranne blew at CERN.
I would never have been banned? Looks like there.
লন্ডন বিশৃঙ্খলার আগুন আছে ... -এখন যথেষ্ট. এ্যাম্বাসেডর!
আমরা ফেডারেশনের দেশের গর্বিত।
এখানে সবাই সম্মান সঙ্গে কথা বলতে হয়েছে।
মাফ করবেন. ম্যাডাম সেক্রেটারি জেনারেল ড। -আমরা এখানে একটি যুদ্ধ ঝুনা আছে।
জনাব ফিন শেপার্ড।
বিভিন্ন স্থান যেখানে কেউ হয়েছে চলেছি।
এই উভয়সঙ্কট অবস্থা আমাদের Valistakaa।
আপনি ঝড় underestimating হয়. এই রেনল্ডস ও অ্যাস্ট্রো-এক্স যেমন ঘটবে।
তারা নিঃস্ব উধাও হয়ে গেছে।
এই প্রাণে বেঁচে যান. এটা ভয়ের কারণে হওয়া উচিত।
এর পরিবর্তে. আসুন আমেরিকা মহান আবার করতে আমাদের ক্রোধ মনে করা যাক।
শুধু যতদিন তুমি আমাকে অনুসরণ. বিশ্বের আবার বড় হবে।
কিভাবে এটি উপর একটি যুদ্ধ হুমকির বিরুদ্ধে? -Aseitamme জ্ঞান ও প্রস্তুতি আছে।
Each new hainado last big. stronger and more noticeable.
We have to anticipate their development. -Kehittyvätkö they seemed like a monkey?
Unless you can prove the validity of the truth ... -Jo hainadoista ancestors suffered.
They won. This permits.
Oh my goodness ..
They wanted to give us information. but it is the first selvättävä.
Nova. kiwi!
Mr. Prime Minister. you live!
It will come back! What did you two do?
Where did it come from? Hard to say. but close.
This is where the Gil.
হেলগা. päivänvarjoni!
NATOnado from the Se!
Thorns. and the angel of my colleagues. Mr. Shepard can save your son.
Let's go. But -Tulkaa!
Speed ​​of 850 kilometers per hour.
I have enough energy to reach the destination. -Shepard. let's go.
If you gain access to our kyyntiin. Dr. Angel over there waiting for us.
Airship? It hindenabarga XP 3000!
Ai hindenabarga? Yes. a bad name.
But it takes a storm? -Kestää.
Where Wobbegon? He -Hainado nirhasi.
What is tragic. -Nobody is irreplaceable.
Ladies and gentlemen. welcome. Nice to meet you. Dr. Angel.
How can I help you? -boy hainadon the maelstrom.
We'll have to wait out a storm.
Voimmehan open its magnetic ionigeneraattorilla.
I've learned one thing after another bartender school.
Magnet activation. It helps?
We are in need of protection. hainadon if we go directly to the eye.
Safe empty. -Vannon. something that was not.
Let's close. not hainadon eyes. It's too late.
What happens then? We just hit hainadoon.
There is a problem.
Tri-angel!
Get out of here! Hainadon missing!
wait.
Oh. the humanity.
Did you fall? সুন্দর -Thanks.
Come on! "We have to get hainadon aboard."
Right this way!
Get down.
Uh. no. Gil will save.
So we can see ghosts Hainado is broken.
This is used for.
It is late. -April. the pitch used by the driver.
We moved to the inside so that it is closer to the hainadoa.
I am not a man to be helicopters. As a result -Try. Gil.
OK. Go to the shelter. Come on.
Yes it is that you will be successful.
Rotation. April. rotate!
As Wonder Woman. Although smaller or lighter -Even.
From Jee!
Mountain liikkuu.- April. stop!
Let's run away!
Now. let's go.
"Father. I will leave you a message. Everything is all right.
Neighbor Steven handle the job puolestani.- I heard what you said.
I think he has stuck with the grandmother. Prevailaing I heard. and this is näreet.
It was a hot pack. The colonel is -Claudia NASA.
Mother and Gilille said. Listen to you soon.
If you're trying to Haitako peer? It's a bad habit. I guess.
Are you okay? Gil is a whirlpool.
It's moving away from us.
Not long.
Quick! Kurimus will end.
We're almost there. Now let's go to the maelstrom!
Gil!
Gil. where are you? -Do you see him?
I do not know. -No not be able to be here.
Gil! She did not come out.
He is probably still hainadossa. Or there.
We're in Australia?
How on earth we were in Australia we do?
Hello. Please Help! -Here!
What are you doing in the water? What?
Do not fall! Watershed full of sharks.
Be still. We release the rope.
There it is. Come on.
To swim.
Last!
On. come on! Your hand!
Do not!
Australia's east coast is full valmiustilassa- -
- prepare for the storm and rescue services. Carl?
Storm warning has been given to the Sydney area.
Winds of 90 km per hour. Hold on to your swimming suit.
Now. you'd run well. -And take shelter.
Kyberteknologiaa hospital can be remedied. but the arms can specialize.
höykytä করবেন না. -Sorry.
So let me talking.
Ursa! Code Red.
who are they? Your doctor -Are? -Fin. they are cleverer doctor.
I will not leave my wife alone. -You are always around me.
Yes. they'd better care. Be in good hands -You'll.
How does it feel? -Nice to explore. ma'am.
You adventure have experienced in a while. -Kurjat tutustumisolosuhteet.
Quite a mess of wires. -Ihan anyone was yrittänyt- -
- stick to the Commodore 54 and MacBook Pro hard disk.
Who are you to put together? -Isäni.
Men Tyypillistä.-. Yes it's here. honey.
We will fix you up. At the same time -Voisitteko forced me ...
Less like a robot? I have experience of this kind.
My mother is a magical grip. -No. no. it's not my way.
I need a zoning digital amplifiers. But not Cyberdyne.
Have you talked with your sisters? Outside is in standby mode.
How do you afford this? -We do not have to. This work is a cover.
Sisarkuntaamme leaders. doctors and even found naked.
I heard what you said. So -Teette work with the government.
We do not. We are effective.
What is it? It looks like that is where all hainadosisaret.
I have to warn your connection to China.
Do not get angry. What?
Appoint my cousin. So this is a cult.
Gemini had the opportunity to do in Las Vegas. He always has a sister.
Do not look good. Do not tell me you -Why?
I know you and I know you will not let me put your family in danger.
Gemini. what China looks like? -We are 15 km from the cyclone.
I'll be back when we are sheltered.
Gemini? Try another extension.
The wind was stronger. then crashed ship.
Go wait for me to safety. No. pollutant emissions can not be allowed to happen.
What did you say? -Hitto. the connection was broken.
If you do not komentele kinsmen! She is a member of the municipality's sister.
He is my cousin! -Heitä needed. It is now the most important thing ...
Save my son! -Pelastaa world!
Or that way. Nova same team we were before.
I do not listen to you anymore. because you are always so short-sighted.
Unless your relative will be here. at some times. some pyörittäisit.
Oh really? What. Nova?
These are hainadot.
Just because you have one of the abolition of the death ukkisi want to kill all the sharks.
Sisterhood that they risk their lives because of it?
If you've always lusted storm of revenge is just an obstacle.
Now the main task is to free the power of the artifact.
Yes. I hate more than anything else sharks!
When they are destroyed. these things can not be seen.
Maybe then we can live a life where someone dies can rakkaistamme.
I think we are on the same side.
Do not let them fall! Please Help!
Give them rope. "-We do not have time.
We made it yes.
We are not safe here. All inside.
10 000 tonnes of nuclear contamination. I'm not leaving until I know of that fairy-tale.
Now. inside. or you can not die for! -Jollei committed to this. to everyone.
Bring it. I've missed you.
Haikaloja. Se থেকে alkaa আয়না haikaloilla.
Apr ...
Say something. -Don't.
Flight module could not be repaired. But we kyberkinetiikan has been updated.
You no longer need to download. -You are living solar battery.
You can control all of your hands.
What do you think? Awesome -You're.
Varovaisia.- to be a short circuit can cause additional power.
Indeed. just a kiss? -Niinkö do you think?
Alkakoon not just the physical. Shaking -You're.
He receives no signal. What it come from?
Gil? It was Gil. See.
Where is he? In this way -Coming.
Re-determination began. Let's see whether this building is supportive of her mission.
now? No. this is not a mere opera house.
Now. stuck!
We have breaking news. -Roger. shows.
We see this as the Sydney Opera House. and we thought opera house.
After all. it collapses. No. change it.
Why did it change? avautuvat- Cover -
- and they will be some of the weapons. -Onpa special.
I thought it was just ylimainostetuksi architecture.
Shell 2 and 3 are stuck. Is it serious?
All steps should be taken. Orion Report.
Yet another shell out of order. Not good. not good.
The number two and number three is still locked. They should not be released manually.
The hawk. I'm in position.
You can open them? The exact location will be the cover.
No way. You will need to disconnect the cable. The churn Gil -Is?
It is a bit like a Bagel. Hainado protect vortex.
How to get there inside? -Hänet will be sought from there.
Benjiköysi. Ignored. Gil was captured. and the rope pull us back up.
Then. set hainadon shell edge. You more easily get inside.
Elikkä ... মুহূর্ত এসেছে.
Please bring me what I aikaisemmin. Please also like to apologize for.
We are flesh and blood. but the same family. however. is not quite the same.
Remember it.
Make your son now. I'm fighting. Visually vibrant.
According to Nova. to be here in five minutes hainado.
Use ceiling ropes. Good luck.
Fire!
Come on.
Envelopes should be shot in the air in order to create a barrier.
It also push the storm at sea. Turn Paxson initiative.
I count. Three. two. one.
Kurimus aukeaa!
He took the artifact.
Now. fried shark tastes!
Plumpsahtamaan again ready with me? Let's go.
Gil!
I see you!
Where are we?
Rio de Janeiro. apparently.
You received this artifact. This will help us to find Gil.
Shepard Finn! USA's greatest hero!
For this chick in love with my friend. Come on. if you want to find your son.
Gilistä How do you know? -Nova sent me.
He followed all the time about going. -Minut has been identified.
Hainadokin where you are always present. How is it possible?
Hundred percent.
I'll Vegalle. What is it?
Who does that mean? Get in the car.
This is suspicious. Come on.
Vega! Guest.
Welcome.
Can I help you? How does it work?
Where is it? -Stonehengestä.
The universe is mathematical. Ancestors knew it.
The system is designed to hainadoja.
Some age-old security system? Here -Miekkavalas. Be prepared.
Each system has a lock to maintain the secret stone.
No one falls into the wrong hands. then we will all be gone.
It should not be sent back to Stonehenge. It is submerged.
Then go swimming. Any other way -Ain't?
Peru or Egypt will take it. why? A world of many ports.
But it's all very different.
Must comply with the rules. Go back to where it all began.
It is not fast. As long as you have a rock -
- hainadon can be achieved by itself.
আমি সময় hainadon পেতে পারি? এটা করতে -কীভাবে?
ফোকাস এবং ঘনত্ব যেমন দেখা দেয় দুটো কারণে বাইরে অন্য চিন্তা।
আমি আপনাকে দেখাতে পারবেন না।
কোথায় পাথর হল?
চলো।
অপেক্ষা করুন।
কাদের ঘূর্ণযন্ত্র চাইছে?
আমরা ব্যাপক ও ধ্বংস কর প্রভাব না!
গিল! তাকে -Menetämme। ব্রেকিং ভূত।
কিছু করবেন না। -আমি না।
আপনি কি জানেন?
সে কোথায় যাচ্ছে?
আমি তাকে দেখতে পারবেন না।
সড়ে যাও। -আমি পাথর প্রয়োজন।
এই আপনি কি এটাই চাও?
আসা এবং এটি গ্রহণ করা। কিছু আছে কোন সময়। আমার ছেলে বিপদের মধ্যে আছে।
এখন আমি দেখাব। -Fin. এটা কাটা।
গাড়ির মাধ্যমে সময়ের সাথে।
অ্যালান ইতিমধ্যে এই সময়ে বেশ ভাল হবে। -Follow hainadoa।
ওইখানে!
না না!
না না।
গিল! -না অভিশাপ. এটা বন্ধ।
আমি আর জানি না কি করতে হবে তা।
দুঃখিত।
তিন কয়েন দাও। জন্য -কি?
এই Fontana. দ্বি Trevi হয়। আশা হতে পারে।
কয়েন কাঁধ ধরে নিক্ষিপ্ত. এবং তারপর আশা পূর্ণ হলো।
আমি কিছুই চেষ্টা করতে ইচ্ছুক নই। রোমের -When হয় ...
Tule.-কোথায়? আমাদের ছেলের ফিরে -Haetaan।
জনাব শেপার্ড। কে তুমি?
একজন ব্যক্তি তোমার সাথে দেখা করতে চায়। -আমি সময় hainado-বোন নেই
এর কি জিনিস সে on.-It এ অনুশোচনা করি না কটাক্ষপাত করা যাক।
কি hainado-বোন?
সে উদ্দেশ্যই বা যার জন্য আমি মনে করি তিনি চলবে? কিছু আছে।
সুতরাং মহান haimetsästäjä হয়।
ঝুঁকি টাইপ oloinen।
আমাকে বাবা মাফ করবেন. আমি ডানা জন্য।
ইতিহাস চমকের পূর্ণ। কিছুই ফয়সালা করে না।
পোপ ভ্যাটিকান রপ্তানি করা উচিত নয়। সেখানে যে কোন মুহুর্তে একটি ঝড় আসতে পারে।
তিনি আপনাকে এখানে আনতে একটি কারণ ছিল। -Imartelevaa- -
- কিন্তু আমি একটি পরিকল্পনা সঙ্গে আসা পর্যন্ত আছে। -হয়তো আপনি একই পরিকল্পনা আছে।
এটা আমার ছেলের সাথে কি আছে তবে আমি শুনছি।
এখন মানবতা রক্ষা করার শেষ সুযোগ।
আপনি ওখানে কি করছ? আমার ছেলে -Pelastan।
তারপর বিশ্বের সংরক্ষণ।
আমি সুযোগ মিস না করতে যাচ্ছি।
পিটার. এই বিরক্তিকর মশা। -আমাদের মজা আছে পছন্দ করেছে।
আমরা মধুচন্দ্রিমা আছে। একটু বল খেলা যাক এবং তারপর আমরা হোটেল এ যান।
তুমি জানো আমি palloillasi সাথে খেলতে পছন্দ করি।
মিথুন নোভা আমন্ত্রণ জানায়।
আমরা দূষণের কোর অনুসরণ করুন। এটা তোলে জীব কিছু রুপান্তরিত হয়েছে।
Olioksiko? -এটা কিছু অনুভব বলে মনে হচ্ছে না।
এটি শুধু একটি বিশাল haimöykky আছে। অপেক্ষা করুন ... এটা দিক পরিবর্তন করে।
সৃষ্টিকর্তা ... এটা জাপান যাচ্ছে।
জীবনের Gilistä লক্ষণ আছে কি? সুদর্শন কিছু আছে করে।
আমরা তাকে খুঁজছেন যখন hainado হবে। আমি একটা কথা শিখেছি করেছি।
এটি তাই সার্ফিং যেমন সময়জ্ঞান সম্পর্কে। তরঙ্গ গতি আবিষ্কার করুন।
আমরা শক্তি. যেখানে গিল hainadossa হয়. থেকে এটা খুঁজে বের করতে হবে - -
- এটা এ যান এবং তারপর আমরা তাকে নিয়ে যাব।
আমি আশা করি এটা জ্ঞান করে তোলে। -Do আপনি এখন ইন্দ্রিয় বানাতে চান?
এটা যে পাথর এক hainadon শুরু করতে পারেন কঠিন।
আমি চাই না যে গিল চিরকাল hainadoon হারিয়ে গেছে।
মনে রাখবেন আমি কি ভেগা বলেন। কিছু মনে করবেন না।
কাউন্ট এর সময়!
এটা সবচেয়ে ভাল হয় যে আমি hainadoon যান। আমার শরীর যে উদ্দেশ্যে নির্মিত মত হল।
হ্যাঁ. আপনি আমাকে অনেক শক্তিশালী করছি। আমাকে টানুন আউট যখন গিল otteessani হয়।
এটা একটা সত্য. তারপর দড়ি। -আমি আমার খপ্পর পেতে যাচ্ছে না।
আপনাকে ধন্যবাদ. পোপ!
Näen kurimuksen!
বাতাসে উড়া করা হবে না!
সেখানে তিনি নেই! -Honey!
চলো. গিল! চলো. ছেলে!
প্রায়! টটেনহ্যাম।
শুধু একটু আরো।
এখন. বাড়ি যাই।
আমরা শুধু সম্পর্কে তাকে পেতে ছিল। -Look।
তিনি এখনও বেঁচে আছেন। তাকে পেতে যাই।
ইতিমধ্যে ছিলো বিশাল হাঙ্গর হয়। -এটা কিছুই হাঙ্গর নয়।
আমরা যদি haizilla।
স্টিভেন. সহায়তা. ঝড় আসে। কালীন কার্ড চালু আছে।
অপেক্ষা করুন। এই থেকে এসেছেন।
আমি আমার দৃষ্টিভঙ্গি দেখতে হবে? বাইরের সম্ভব।
দেখা যাক Xfinity স্ট্রিম অ্যাপ দেখতে কেমন।
hainado কিভাবে উত্তর আমেরিকায় আপনার পরিবার প্রভাবিত করেছে?
আমি কানাডা একটি পিসতুত ভাই ছিল ... -না টক আনত খবর বলুন।
... এবং এখন ছয় ফুট এবং ...
Hainadoja এখন সর্বত্র। আমরা জাপান থেকে ভয়ঙ্কর খবর পেয়েছিলাম।
সরাসরি টোকিও. শিকাগো আজকের প্রতিবেদক হাওয়ার্ড বিয়েল থেকে।
বিশ্বের ধ্বংসের কিনারা হয়। এই রহস্যোদ্ঘাটন আরেকটি লক্ষণ।
আমি জানি না কি এটা। বিশাল দুর্গন্ধযুক্ত সবকিছু খাওয়া haimössö।
তাই যে sucks হয়।
HAIZILLA আক্রমণ টোকিও
গিল যে ভিতরে হয়। -কি এখন আমরা করব?
হিংস্র কি!
আইন. এক রান. 5 000 জন্য অবশিষ্ট আছে। একটি উচ্চ স্তরের করার জন্য!
বোন. এটি একটি মিথোজীবী haiolento কে জানে বিন্যাস পরিবর্তন করতে কিভাবে হয়।
এটা অঙ্কুর যাক. এটা কেটে riehutaan পর্যন্ত এটি আর বিদ্যমান নেই।
কিন্তু হুঁশিয়ার. খুব ঘনিষ্ঠ যেতে না. যে এটা Gilille যেমন ঘটবে।
এটা আমার দোষ যে গিল একটি ঝোল হয়। আমি তাকে বাঁচানোর পেয়েছেন।
মনে রাখবেন যে যখন আপনি একটি হাঙ্গর দেখতে. ডানা উপলব্ধি।
এখন. তাদের শিটস nirhaamaan যাই।
এটা সম্ভবত নোভা হয়। তিনি -কি কাজ করে?
আমাদের ছেলের সংরক্ষণ করুন!
গিল!
চলো।
সেখানে স্তব্ধ হয়ে যেতে!
নোভা. সৌভাগ্য। কোন উপায় আপনার পরিদর্শন করা নেই।
না চিন্তা করতে. আপনি খারাপ মাধ্যমে চলেছি। এটা তোলে জর্জেস বার খারাপ ছিল না।
টটেনহ্যাম। ক্লান্ত -I'm।
আমার দিকে তাকাও। ফোকাস। আমি যে জন্য খুবই দুঃখিত।
হ্যাঁ. আপনি তাদের ব্যবহার। ছেড়ে দিতে হবে না। নোভা?
আপনি শুনতে পেলেন? গিল অতীতের একটি জিনিস।
সে মারা গেছে।
আমি আমার সেরাটা করেনি। মাফ করে দিও।
আমি দুঃখিত ... -Don't ছেড়ে দিতে হবে।
ফাইট. নোভা। হ্যাঁ গিল বাস।
এই বেঁচে থাকতে. নোভা। আমিও হারান. চাই না।
নোভা!
ফিন ... আমরা আত্নীয় করছে ...
একই পরিবারের। এ-ধরনের পরিবার।
এখন এই বিশ্বে প্রতিবেদক রন ম্যাকডোনাল্ড থেকে সর্বশেষ খবর।
আফ্রিকা উন্নয়ন উদ্বেজক suuntaan.-রন যাচ্ছে?
ঝড় সিংহ ও কৃষ্ণসার পর্যন্ত সময় লাগতে হবে!
এখন শুধু মাত্র হাঙ্গর ও সিংহের যারা কৃষ্ণসার তাড়া পেছনে তাড়া।
আমরা যদি safarinado!
মার্কিন সর্বকালের সবচেয়ে খারাপ myrskyyn- প্রস্তুতি নিচ্ছে -
- সময় কি আপনি বলতে আলী এটি সম্পর্কে কথা শুনতে আসা হয়েছে।
এখানে তা যায় কিভাবে আছে: hainado অন্য teareth Eurooppaa- পর -
- এবং মার্কিন নিজস্ব হুমকি ছবি হয়েছে। টেক্সাস তারিখ থেকে দেশ।
সান ফ্রান্সিস্কো ক্যালিফোর্নিয়া আকার মত ধ্বংসাবশেষ রয়েছে।
মিডওয়েস্ট বড় অংশের ধ্বংস হয়ে গেছে।
নিউ ইয়র্ক পূর্ব উপকূল যা এখনও আক্রান্ত করা হয়েছে শুধুমাত্র শহর।
কিন্তু আমরা শুনেছি hainado বরাবর myrskytietä- যাচ্ছে -
- এশিয়া ইন্টারঅ্যাক্টিভ দিকে আবার তাদের পথে সম্প্রদায়ের অন্তক।
শুধুমাত্র প্রথম আক্রমণের মত শুধু একটি পরীক্ষা হত।
এই শেষ মার্কিন বরং সারা বিশ্বের জন্য না শুধুমাত্র বানান পারে।
আমি আবার এখানে আছি। কোথায় raye-ঠাকুরমা হয়? ভিতরে কিছু আছে।
Raye! -Mummi. না!
এর এখান থেকে বের করা যাক।
স্টিভ. আমার হাত ধরো।
ম্যাট! আমার হাতে -Tartu!
না!
ম্যাট। বাবা!
আমি সব রক্ষার চেষ্টা করে। Mynkään গেলেন।
ঠাকুরমা ও স্টিভেন মারা যান।
কোথাও আর নিরাপদ হতে পারে না। -মথি!
কর্নেল. ক্লদিয়া. সমস্ত মারা গেছে। -না. ম্যাট। শুনুন।
বাবা. আমি তোমাকে ভালবাসি!
ম্যাট!
সব চলে গেছে ... চলে গেছে।
কোন ... -না. এই এইভাবে শেষ হয়ে আসতে পারে।
সব পরে যে আমরা অনুভব না।
নেই সব উত্সর্গমূলক. সমস্ত লোকসান পরে।
যতদিন আমরা একসাথে আছি. এটা শেষ হয়নি।
বাজি এক একটি আবশ্যক।
এর Sonehengeen যাই। হস্তনির্মিত বস্তু পুনর্বহালের।
আমরা আর খেললে হারতে হবে আরো।
হিসাবে সম্পন্ন করা হয়।
এখন. যদি কখনও।
ডানা. varo!
পিতা?
গিল! আমি এখানে. গিল।
এপ্রিল. আমি গিল পাওয়া যায় নি!
গিল. আমার হাত ধরো।
এখন ইংল্যান্ডে হ্যা না। -আমরা নেভিগেট করতে শিখতে হবে।
যে প্রতীক আবার। "বিশ্বের অনেক পোর্ট রয়েছে।"
চলো।
Haijumala। এই স্থানটি স্টোনহেঞ্জ মনে করিয়ে দেয়।
একটি লক যেমন Druids হস্তনির্মিত বস্তু কি? হ্যা।
সম্ভবত মিশরীয়রা একটি কী হিসেবে ব্যবহার করেন।
এই ধরুন।
চলো।
এই কার্নেল প্রদর্শন করবে।
মিশরীয়রা মেশিনের পথনির্দেশক কোর ছিলেন। এটি চালু করুন।
আপনি একই আমি কি হিসাবে মনে করেন?
দেখা যাক।
আবহাওয়া আউট ক্লিয়ারিং হয়!
মিথুন. তুমি ঠিক আছ? -Fin ... আমি সব মৃতের চিন্তা।
ঝড় অনেকটাই স্তিমিত। এটা তোলে এর উপর।
এটি সফলভাবে। -কিন্তু সে নয়।
ম্যাট. ক্লদিয়া. গিল. পুরো পরিবার।
না ...
বিশ্বের কি? এই বিন্দু থেকে এটা মেকিং।
এটা বন্ধ না! -Jumissa!
আমি বন্ধ করতে পারবেন সেন-It এ অত্যধিক শক্তি প্রয়োজন। আপনি মারা যেতে পারে।
বলাই বাহুল্য yrittää.-Yritinhän আপনার খুব. এবং আমি আপনাকে পেয়েছিলাম।
আমি এটা বন্ধ করার পেতে পারে না।
Marijuanado?
Hainadohyökkäys Dusseldorf ধ্বংস হয়েছে!
আবহাওয়ার রাডার ঘোষণা যে বার্লিন hainado সমীপবর্তী হয়।
সিসমিক কার্যকলাপ উপরে verging। এখান থেকে বের -এখন।
এই বন্ধ হবে!
ওহ. সুন্দর ...
ওইখানে!
আমি ঘূর্ণি থামাও. তুমি সুনামি নিষ্কাশন।
আমি অনেক দীর্ঘ সময়ের জন্য না।
বন্ধ করুন!
এপ্রিল ... Kultsi ...
বৈশাখ! Kultsi!
Kultsi!
ওহো. না।
না না।
এপ্রিল ... এখানে হ্যাঁ এটা। সকল খুব ভাল।
দয়া করে. মরে না।
আমরা এই মধু হ্যান্ডেল করব।
না. না. মরে না!
না. এপ্রিল। না!
যে কেউ আছে কি?
আপনি কে?
এটা আমার ছেলে অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। আপনি কি তাকে করেছ?
আরে. বাবা। কিছু আছে সম্ভব হতে পারে।
সর্বদা প্রস্তুত।
Shephard সবসময় প্রস্তুত। -না।
এই ব্যাখ্যা করা কঠিন। আমি পথে আপনাকে বলতে হবে।
কোথায়? -Sinne যেখানে এটা সব শুরু করে।
শুধুমাত্র তারপর আমরা বাবা. পরিবার এবং বিশ্বের সংরক্ষণ করতে পারবেন। বাবা. আমাকে বিশ্বাস
এটা সত্যিই আপনি. গিল আছে কি?
আমার পুত্র!
আমি জানতাম। আপনি কিভাবে টোকিও বিস্ফোরণ টেকা হয়নি?
এটা আমার সময় ফেরত পাঠিয়েছে। বছরের পর বছর ধরে দাবি ফিরে ফিরে যান।
তাই আপনি যদি hainadosta টাইম মেশিন তৈরি।
Jep.-জন্য আইন এটা আমার ছেলে ... আমার স্বামী।
কিন্তু প্রশংসা।
এটা এই উদ্দেশ্যে দেওয়া ড্রাইভিং লাইসেন্স আছে? সেখানে -Not. যেখানে আমরা যাচ্ছি।
অব্যাহত ...
অনুবাদ: Hakan মধ্যে Mäkelä www.OrdioVision.com
www.moviesubtitles.org